So,
on your side? I've honestly had a really great
experience with AI in the lab, because,
and I think the reason I've had a really great
experience is because I've
taken an extra step to understand
what AI is doing, which I could talk more about
that, but this experience is, I've been using
AI to parse through a lot of the data,
or a lot of what's been written about the Cub
Excel to help me understand it.
music building.
You'll need to go that way.
Yeah.
Past the Wilk. Yeah. Pass the Wilk.
Yes, sorry.
But, so I'll,
it'll help me understand what's been written
already in
Alex's, like, whole
GitHub repository of, like, Cubware,
CubOS, and help me understand how to use that
tool to where now I understand the
machinery. of a Gantry, which I didn't before.
Okay. I understand the
YAML files that go into the
protocols that we do and how to write those myself.
Okay. And so when I ping -clad to do these things,
I know exactly what it's doing.
Gotcha. And right now I'm still running low -level
things on the Cub XL, so maybe that's why I've
had such
success with it, because I'm not needing it to
do very high -level things.
Gotcha.
But I have found great success with that.
So in some sense, maybe the fact that you're
starting with a
low -level project where you will get to the
higher -level stuff, but you're kind of getting
in this, in the synchronization with Claw,
like,
I think as you you go to the higher levels, you'll
just keep that same kind of dialogue going.
Yeah. And I started from, like, the ground up
where, like, I knew nothing and I was
building something to where I feel like...
Like you literally built the machine.
Exactly. Yeah, I literally built the machine,
and so I had to understand.
I think, like, people Well, coming into the lab
in a semester when things have been built, I'm
worried that they might fall into the flow where
we are using high -level AI,
and they're just kind of like, I never got the
chance to learn any of this.
Yeah. Yeah. And I don't know how we're going
to balance that. Yeah.
And then the feedback cycle can
become,
that didn't work, try again.
Yeah. That didn't work, try again.
It's, yeah, not really.
I think on my side,
when I think about a
little bit of, I think about a little.
I think about a little. I think about.
I don't work, learning,
like, an experience where it helped me learn
something.
What's, what's funny is a lot of this is coming
from not AI or Claude
or Co -Pilot being the one who's teaching me,
but rather, I'm trying to learn something in
my use of it. Yeah. Because I get super
excited about finding some trick,
some cool way that I can use it that I can use
it that I haven't been able to before.
And so, like, a recent one was,
this trick that we'll be using for this.
Kind of the reason we're recording this video
is, we'll upload this video to YouTube.
I have it so that that that YouTube video can
get downloaded along with the transcript
and then have Claude segment things out and take
screenshots. I mean, that won't apply in this
case, like for the screenshotshots, but if you're
doing like a
feedback of a paper or
reviewing anything where
there's, like, you're doing like a feedback of
a paper or reviewing anything there's a visual
component and an auditory component or like a,
your own feedback and then some visual thing,
like, just makes a whole spec document
with screenshots and your timestamped comments
that it can then go and iterate through sort
of thing. And that just, that feels like a freeing
thing because you can just
talk. Yes. And click and point
and you don't have to write down everything that
you're... Yeah, yeah, and I tell it to, uh...
Like,
if there's some reference to where the mouse
is pointing, take a burst of screenshots so that
you can correlate things back to the mouse,
like, pointer on it and so, just something like
that. And I find that kind of fun, fun and
exciting on things. I think I've also,
um,
one thing I'd like to do better with,
or maybe some things I'd like to like to explore
and learn more about is getting into some of
the powder metallurgy stuff with the, with the
powder workflows is how can I,
yeah, have that kind of deeper scientific metallurgy.
Like, as in you understanding that more, you're,
you understanding how to use AI more in that?
Oh, no, to, like, actually understand the science
better for some of those.
I think that,
uh, I've gleaned things, but I think having
some more time, it's like,
here's this thing, I really want to dig in and
understand all the nuances of this.
Like, what, what do the, what do the, what are
the mechanisms, what are,
what's going on at the physics level, when often
I can take such a, like, so application,
like,
well, who cares if we know how, like, how it
works if we can't get it to work, like, how it
works if we can't get it to work, but yeah, it
goes both ways, so that's kind of, anyway,
anyway, should probably, yeah, just back.